// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is a correct definition of coastal zone?",
    answer: "C. It is where land meets the sea.",
    options: [
      "A. It is where people spend their vacation.",
      "B. It is where destructive waves are common.",
      "C. It is where land meets the sea.",
      "D. It is where sharks and whales are observed.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT an example of coastal processes?",
    answer: "D. Transportation",
    options: [
      "A. Deposition",
      "B. Erosion",
      "C. Plucking",
      "D. Transportation",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following are examples of coastal erosion?",
    answer: "C. Corrasion, abrasion, hydraulic action, attrition and corrosion/solution",
    options: [
      "A. Corrasion, abrasion, hydraulic action, attrition and suspension.",
      "B. Corrasion, abrasion, wave action, attrition and corrosion/solution",
      "C. Corrasion, abrasion, hydraulic action, attrition and corrosion/solution",
      "D. Corrasion, abrasion, hydraulic action, attrition and traction",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which type of coastal erosion involves destructive waves picking up beach material hurling them at the base of a cliff?",
    answer: "A. Corrasion",
    options: [
      "A. Corrasion",
      "B. Hydraulic action",
      "C. Attrition",
      "D. Abrasion",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Itâ€™s also known as the sandpaper effect that involves breaking waves containing sand and bigger fragments eroding the base of a cliff.",
    answer: "D. Abrasion",
    options: [
      "A. Corrasion",
      "B. Hydraulic action",
      "C. Attrition",
      "D. Abrasion",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Kind of coastal erosion that involves waves hitting the bottom of the cliff causing air to be compressed in cracks, joints, and folds in bedding planes leading to repeated changes in air pressure.",
    answer: "B. Hydraulic action",
    options: [
      "A. Corrasion",
      "B. Hydraulic action",
      "C. Attrition",
      "D. Abrasion",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which type of coastal erosion occurs when waves cause rocks and pebbles to bump into each other and break up?",
    answer: "C. Attrition",
    options: [
      "A. Corrasion",
      "B. Hydraulic action",
      "C. Attrition",
      "D. Abrasion",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which type of coastal erosion occurs when certain types of cliff erode as a result of weak acids in the sea?",
    answer: "A. Corrasion/ solution",
    options: [
      "A. Corrasion/ solution",
      "B. Hydraulic action",
      "C. Corrasion",
      "D. Abrasion",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a factor that affects rates of coastal erosion?",
    answer: "C. The greenhouse effect",
    options: [
      "A. Geology",
      "B. Strong winds blowing for a long time creating destructive waves",
      "C. The greenhouse effect",
      "D. Wave fetch",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How are waves created?",
    answer: "D. It is created by the wind blowing over the surface of the sea",
    options: [
      "A. It is created by the rain",
      "B. It is created by the water cycle",
      "C. It is created by people in ships",
      "D. It is created by the wind blowing over the surface of the sea",
    ],
  },
];
